Pay to play.
Sugar Baby is a thriller, comedy film directed by Lauren Garroni.
An enterprising Sugar Baby is offered $30,000 to move in with her Sugar Daddy for the
week, but soon discovers the sinister secrets trapped within his home.
Marie, played by Mary Beth Barone.
Chloe, played by Nina Bloomgarden.
Jeff, played by James Tupper.
Eddy, played by Theo Germaine.
Lucky, played by Paige Collins.
Ben, played by Behzad Dabu.
Sugar dating or sugaring is a type of pseudoromantic interpersonal relationship where one
person receives money or gifts in exchange for intimacy or companionship.
The provider (called a sugar daddy or sugar mommy) is typically older and wealthier, while the recipient (called a
sugar baby) is typically younger, attractive, and interested in improving their quality of life.
The recipient can obtain gifts such as jewelry, luxury goods, vacations, fine dining, mentorship, leisure outings, financial
support, and offers social benefits such as companionship, dedication, devotion, affection, dating or intimacy.
Sugar dating is especially popular in the online dating community due
to the easy access to specific niches and desires.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.